ARE YOU READY, KIDS?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
AYE AYE, CAPTAIN!
孩子们：
是啊是，队长！
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
我听不到你说话！
AYE AYE, CAPTAIN!
是啊是，队长！
* OH... *
* 哦... *
* WHO LIVES IN A PINEAPPLE
UNDER THE SEA? *
*谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ *
* SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS! *
* 海绵宝宝！ *
* ABSORBENT AND YELLOW
AND POROUS IS HE *
* 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的*
* SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS! *
* 海绵宝宝！ *
* IF NAUTICAL NONSENSE
BE SOMETHING YOU WISH *
*如果航海废话
成为您所希望的*
* SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS! *
* 海绵宝宝！ *
* THEN DROP ON THE DECK
AND FLOP LIKE A FISH *
* 然后掉到甲板上
像鱼一样扑腾*
* SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS! *
* 海绵宝宝！ *
* READY?
SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS! *
* 准备好？
海绵宝宝！ *
* SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS *
*海绵宝宝*
* SPONGEBOB
SQUAREPANTS *
* 海绵宝宝
方裤 *
* SPONGEBOB... SQUAREPANTS! *
* 海绵宝宝...方裤！ *
( Captain laughs )
（队长笑）
( plays flute tune )
（吹奏长笛曲调）
[Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
[字幕由THE赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON]
和尼克频道]
Frenchman:
AH, THE SEA, SO FASCINATING,
SO WONDERFUL.
法国人：
啊，大海，如此迷人，
太棒了。
HERE WE SEE BIKINI BOTTOM,
TEEMING WITH LIFE
在这里我们看到比基尼底部，
充满生机
HOME OF ONE OF
MY FAVORITE CREATURES:
其中一位的家
我最喜欢的生物：
SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS.
海绵宝宝。
YES, OF COURSE HE LIVES
IN A PINEAPPLE, YOU SILLY.
是的，他当然还活着
在菠萝里，你这个傻瓜。
( snoring )
（打鼾）
( horn blows )
（号角吹响）
( horn stops )
（喇叭停止）
TODAY'S THE BIG DAY, GARY.
今天是个大日子，加里。
( meows )
（喵）
LOOK AT ME!
看着我！
I'M... NAKED!
我……赤身裸体！
GOT TO BE IN TOP PHYSICAL
CONDITION FOR TODAY, GARY.
必须保持最佳体能
今天的情况，加里。
( meows )
（喵）
( breathing deeply )
（深呼吸）
( grunts )
（咕哝声）
( screams )
（尖叫声）
( grunts and screams )
（咕哝声和尖叫声）
( pants )
（ 裤子 ）
( screams  )
（尖叫声）
( gasps )
（喘气）
( bunnies squeak )
（兔子吱吱声）
SpongeBob:
I'M READY!
海绵宝宝：
我准备好了！
I'M READY, I'M READY, I'M READY.
我准备好了，我准备好了，我准备好了。
I'M READY, I'M READY, I'M READY,
I'M READY...
我准备好了，我准备好了，我准备好了，
我准备好了...
GO, SPONGEBOB!
去吧，海绵宝宝！
WHOA...
哇...
( crashes )
（崩溃）
THERE IT IS...
就在那里……
THE FINEST EATING ESTABLISHMENT
最好的餐饮场所
EVER ESTABLISHED FOR EATING.
曾经为食用而设立。
THE KRUSTY KRAB,
HOME OF THE CRABBY PATTY.
脆皮蟹，
蟹肉饼之家。
A HELP WANTED SIGN
IN THE WINDOW.
需要帮助的标志
在窗户里。
FOR YEARS, I'VE DREAMED
OF THIS MOMENT.
多年来，我一直梦想着
这一刻。
I'M GOING TO GO IN THERE,
MARCH STRAIGHT TO THE MANAGER
我要去那里，
直接向经理进军
LOOK HIM IN THE EYE,
LAY IT ON THE LINE
看着他的眼睛，
上线
AND I CAN'T DO THIS!
我不能这样做！
PATRICK!
帕特里克！
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
你认为在哪里
你要去吗？
I WAS JUST...
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
我只是...
不，你不是。
YOU'RE GOING TO
THE KRUSTY KRAB
AND GET THAT JOB!
你将会
脆皮蟹
得到那份工作！
I CAN'T,
DON'T YOU SEE?
我不能，
你不明白吗？
I'M NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
我还不够好。
WHOSE FIRST WORDS WERE,
"MAY I TAKE YOUR ORDER?"
谁的第一句话是，
“我可以接受您的订单吗？”
MINE WERE.
我的是。
WHO MADE A SPATULA
谁制作了抹刀
OUT OF TOOTHPICKS
IN WOOD SHOP?
牙签用完
在木工店？
I DID.
我做到了。
WHO'S...
谁的...
( grunts )
（咕哝声）
WHO'S...
谁的...
WHO'S A BIG,
YELLOW CUBE WITH HOLES?
谁很大，
带孔的黄色立方体？
I AM!
我是！
WHO'S READY?
谁准备好了吗？
I'M READY!
我准备好了！
WHO'S READY?
I'M READY!
谁准备好了吗？
我准备好了！
WHO'S READY?
谁准备好了吗？
I'M READY!
我准备好了！
I'M READY.
我准备好了。
I'M READY, I'M READY...
我准备好了，我准备好了……
I'M READY, I'M READY,
I'M READY!
我准备好了，我准备好了，
我准备好了！
OH, NO. SPONGEBOB!
哦，不。海绵宝宝！
WHAT COULD HE POSSIBLY WANT?
他可能想要什么？
GO, SPONGEBOB!
去吧，海绵宝宝！
GO, SPONGEBOB,
GO, SELF.
去吧，海绵宝宝，
去吧，自我。
( shrieks )
（尖叫声）
MR. KRABS!
先生。螃蟹！
HURRY, MR. KRABS,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
快点，先生。螃蟹，
在为时已晚之前。
SpongeBob:
PERMISSION TO COME ABOARD,
CAPTAIN.
海绵宝宝：
上船许可，
船长。
I'VE BEEN TRAINING MY WHOLE LIFE
我一生都在训练
TO JOIN THE KRUSTY CREW,
AND NOW I'M READY.
加入 Krusty 团队，
现在我准备好了。
( yelping )
（尖叫）
( bouncing and yelping )
（弹跳和叫喊）
AH!
啊！
AH! OOH.
啊！哦。
UM...
嗯...
SO, UH, WHEN DO I START?
那么，呃，我什么时候开始？
LAD, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU DON'T
EVEN HAVE YOUR SEA LEGS.
小伙子，看起来你不这么认为
甚至拥有您的海上腿。
MR. KRABS, PLEASE, I'LL PROVE
I'M FRY COOK MATERIAL.
先生。蟹蟹，拜托，我会证明的
我是炒菜材料。
ASK SQUIDWARD.
问问章鱼哥。
HE'LL VOUCH FOR ME.
他会为我担保。
NO.
不。
WELL, LAD, WE'LL GIVE YOU
A TEST, AND IF YOU PASS
好吧，小伙子，我们会给你
测试，如果你通过了
YOU'LL BE
ON THE KRUSTY CREW.
你会的
关于 Krusty 船员。
GO OUT AND FETCH ME A...
出去给我拿一个……
A... HYDRODYNAMIC SPATULA
A...流体动力抹刀
WITH, UM, PORT AND
STARBOARD ATTACHMENTS
与，嗯，端口和
右舷附件
AND TURBO DRIVE.
和涡轮驱动。
AND DON'T COME BACK
TILL YOU GET ONE.
并且不要回来
直到你得到一个。
AYE AYE, CAPTAIN.
是啊是，队长。
ONE HYDRODYNAMIC
SPATULA
一流体动力
锅铲
PORT AND STARBOARD
ATTACHMENTS,
TURBO DRIVE
左舷和右舷
附件，
涡轮驱动
COMING UP, SIR!
即将到来，先生！
CARRY ON!
继续！
WE'LL NEVER SEE
THAT LUBBER AGAIN.
我们永远不会看到
又是那个润滑液。
YOU'RE TERRIBLE.
你太糟糕了。
A HYDRO WHAT?
水力发电什么？
( laughing )
（笑）
( still laughing... )
（还在笑……）
Driver:
HEY, HEY, PLEASE!
PASSENGERS ARE TO STAY SEATED
司机：
嘿，嘿，拜托！
乘客应留在座位上
AND NOT PUT THEIR HEADS
OUT THE WINDOWS.
不要把头伸过来
窗外。
( laughter inside continues )
（里面的笑声还在继续）
( gasps )
（喘气）
THAT SOUNDED
LIKE HATCH DOORS.
听起来不错
像舱门。
( sniffing )
（嗅）
DO YOU SMELL IT?
你闻到了吗？
THAT SMELL.
那种味道。
A KIND OF SMELLY SMELL.
一种臭味。
A SMELLY SMELL THAT SMELLS...
一股臭味，闻起来……
SMELLY.
臭。
ANCHOVIES.
凤尾鱼。
WHAT?
什么？
ANCHOVIES!
凤尾鱼！
( anchovies clamoring )
（凤尾鱼叫嚷）
PLEASE, PLEASE!
拜托，拜托！
QUIET!
安静的！
IS THIS ANY WAY
TO BEHAVE?
这是什么办法吗？
行为举止？
HMM?
唔？
CAN WE SHOW
A LITTLE DECENCY
我们可以展示吗
一点点正派
AND FORM A NEAT, SINGLE-FILE
LINE IN FRONT OF THE REGISTER?
并形成整齐的单行
寄存器前面有一行吗？
( clamoring hysterically )
（歇斯底里地叫喊）
* BARG'N-MART, MEETING
ALL YOUR SPATULA NEEDS. *
* BARG'N-MART，会议
满足您所有抹刀需求。 *
Krabs:
ALL HANDS ON DECK!
螃蟹：
全体人员齐心协力！
GET YOUR ANCHORS
OUT OF YOUR PANTS!
获得你的锚点
脱光你的裤子！
ONE SINGLE-FILE LINE
IS ALL I ASK!
WHOA!
一根单列线
这就是我所要求的！
哇啊！
WHOA!
BATTEN DOWN THE HATCHES,
MR. SQUIDWARD!
压紧舱门，
先生。章鱼哥！
WE'RE TAKING ON WATER,
MR. SQUIDWARD!
我们正在取水，
先生。章鱼哥！
I WANT MY MOMMY,
MR. SQUIDWARD!
我想要我的妈妈，
先生。章鱼哥！
( humming )
（嗡嗡声）
* SPATULA, SPATULA *
* 抹刀，抹刀 *
* PORT AND STARBOARD
ATTACHMENTS. *
* 左舷和右舷
附件。 *
Squidward:
HELP!
章鱼哥：
救命！
Krabs:
MAN OVERBOARD!
螃蟹：
男子落水！
CLIMB, MR. SQUIDWARD,
CLIMB!
克莱姆先生。章鱼哥，
爬！
THIS IS THE END!
这就是结局！
GOOD-BYE,
MR. SQUIDWARD.
再见，
先生。章鱼哥。
OH, MR. KRABS!
哦，先生。螃蟹！
( sobbing )
（抽泣）
SpongeBob:
PERMISSION TO COME ABOARD,
CAPTAIN.
海绵宝宝：
上船许可，
船长。
* DA-DADADA-DA-DAH! *
* 哒哒哒哒哒哒！ *
DID SOMEONE
ORDER A SPATULA?
有人吗
订购抹刀？
( babbling
incoherently )
（胡言乱语
语无伦次）
THAT'S RIGHT,
ONE HYDRODYNAMIC SPATULA
没错，
一把流体动力抹刀
WITH PORT
AND STARBOARD
ATTACHMENTS
带端口
和右舷
附件
AND LET'S NOT FORGET
THE TURBO DRIVE.
我们不要忘记
涡轮驱动。
WOULD YOU BELIEVE
THEY ONLY HAD
ONE IN STOCK?
你相信吗
他们只有
有现货吗？
TO THE KITCHEN!
到厨房！
WHO'S HUNGRY?
谁饿了？
( anchovies clamor )
（凤尾鱼叫嚣）
Tiny Tim:
* THINGS THAT BOTHER YOU
NEVER BOTHER ME *
小蒂姆：
* 困扰你的事情
永远不要打扰我*
* I'M AS HAPPY AS PIE, HA-HA! *
* 我高兴极了，哈哈！ *
* LIVING IN THE SUNLIGHT,
LOVING IN THE MOONLIGHT *
* 生活在阳光下，
月光下的爱*
* HAVING A WONDERFUL TIME. *
* 度过了一段美好的时光。 *
* HAVEN'T GOT A LOT,
I DON'T NEED A LOT *
* 还没有很多，
我不需要很多 *
* COFFEE'S ONLY A DIME *
* 咖啡只要一毛钱 *
* LIVING IN THE SUNLIGHT,
LOVING IN THE MOONLIGHT *
* 生活在阳光下，
月光下的爱*
* HAVING A WONDERFUL TIME. *
* 度过了一段美好的时光。 *
* JUST TAKE IT FROM ME,
I'M JUST AS FREE
AS ANY BROTHER. *
* 就从我这里拿走吧，
我一样自由
和任何兄弟一样。 *
* I DO WHAT I LIKE
JUST WHEN I LIKE,
AND HOW I LOVE IT. *
* 我做我喜欢做的事
就在我喜欢的时候，
我多么喜欢它。 *
* I'M RIGHT HERE TO STAY,
WHEN I'M OLD AND GRAY *
*我就留在这里，
当我老了、头发花白的时候*
* I'LL BE RIGHT IN MY PRIME *
*我将正值巅峰*
* LIVING IN THE SUNLIGHT,
LOVING IN THE MOONLIGHT *
* 生活在阳光下，
月光下的爱*
* HAVING A WONDERFUL TIME. *
* 度过了一段美好的时光。 *
( trilling the tune )
（颤音）
( blows a musical note )
（吹响一个音符）
THAT WAS THE FINEST
FAST-FOODSMANSHIP
那是最好的
快餐精神
I'VE EVER SEEN,
MR. SQUAREPANTS.
先生。 SQUAREPANTS.
WELCOME ABOARD.
欢迎登机。
BUT MR. KRABS...
但是先生。螃蟹...
THREE CHEERS
FOR SPONGEBOB!
三声欢呼
为了海绵宝宝！
HIP, HIP...
髋关节，髋关节...
HOORAY.
MR. KRABS...
万岁。
先生。螃蟹...
HIP, HIP...
HOORAY.
髋关节，髋关节...
万岁。
HIP, HIP...
髋关节，髋关节...
HOORAY. MR. KRABS...
万岁。先生。螃蟹...
I'LL BE
IN MY QUARTERS
我会的
在我的宿舍里
COUNTING UP THE BOOTY.
数着战利品。
GOOD MORNING, KRUSTY CREW!
早上好，Krusty 船员！
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO ORDER, PATRICK?
你想要什么
要订购吗，帕特里克？
ONE CRABBY
PATTY, PLEASE.
一只螃蟹
帕蒂，请。
( crashing )
（崩溃）
Squidward:
MR. KRABS, MR. KRABS!
章鱼哥：
先生。克拉布斯先生。螃蟹！
MR. KRABS, COME SEE
YOUR NEW EMPLOYEE.
先生。蟹蟹，快来看看
您的新员工。
* LIVING IN THE SUNLIGHT,
LOVING IN THE MOONLIGHT *
* 生活在阳光下，
月光下的爱*
* HAVING A WONDERFUL TIME! *
* 玩得很开心！ *
( whistles casually )
（随意吹口哨）
( motor throbbing... )
（电机颤动……）
( grumbles )
（抱怨）
( coughs )
（咳嗽）
( motor starts,
then dies )
（电机启动，
然后死了）
( gasps )
（喘气）
( buzzing like a bee )
（像蜜蜂一样嗡嗡作响）
WOW, FOUR STINGERS.
哇，四个毒刺。
( buzzing )
（嗡嗡声）
OH!
哦！
( girl yelling )
（女孩大喊）
( yelling )
（大喊）
( gasps )
（喘气）
( grunting... )
（咕哝……）
WHERE HAVE I SEEN THIS BEFORE?
我以前在哪里见过这个？
HERE IT IS--
这里是 -
LAND SQUIRREL.
陆松鼠。
THAT LITTLE SQUIRREL
IS IN TROUBLE.
那只小松鼠
有麻烦了。
TAKE THAT, YOU SORRY OLD CLAM.
拿着这个，你这个对不起的老蛤。
YOU NEED TO LEARN SOME MANNERS.
你需要学习一些礼仪。
YOU'RE ABOUT AS UGLY
AS HOMEMADE SOUP.
你也同样丑陋
作为自制汤。
HOORAY, LAND SQUIRREL!
万岁，地松鼠！
( growls )
（咆哮）
LOOK OUT!
当心！
( grunting... )
（咕哝……）
HOLD ON, LITTLE SQUIRREL!
坚持住，小松鼠！
( karate yell )
（空手道大喊）
HO-HO-HO-HO!
嗬-嗬-嗬-嗬！
HO-HEE!
呵呵！
HOY-YA!
嘿呀！
YOU HAVE FOUGHT WELL,
GIANT CLAM.
你打得很好，
巨蛤。
PREPARE TO BE VANQUISHED.
准备好被征服吧。
( yells, grunting... )
（喊叫、咕噜声……）
HEY, I'M ACTUALLY DOING IT.
嘿，我真的在做。
( grunting... )
（咕哝……）
( victorious yell )
（胜利的呐喊）
YOUR SHELL IS MINE!
你的壳是我的！
( grunts )
HOLD ON THERE,
LITTLE SQUARE DUDE.
（咕哝声）
坚持住，
小方块家伙。
( karate yell )
（空手道大喊）
( yells )
（大喊）
( clam whimpers )
（蛤蜊呜咽声）
HEY, YOU LIKE
KARATE, TOO.
嘿，你喜欢
空手道也是如此。
( karate yelling... )
（空手道大喊……）
HA!
哈！
SO, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
那么，你叫什么名字？
SANDY.
沙。
SO, WHAT... DO... YOU...
CALL YOURSELF?
那么，你...做什么...
给自己打电话？
( yelling ):
I'M SPONGEBOB!
（大喊）：
我是海绵宝宝！
WELL, SPONGEBOB...
嗯，海绵宝宝...
TAKE A GANDER AT THIS.
看看这个。
( rumbling, cracking... )
（隆隆声、破裂声……）
OH.
哦。
OH, YEAH?
哦，是吗？
WATCH THIS.
注意这个。
( yells )
（大喊）
( armpit-farts )
（腋下放屁）
( giggles )
I LIKE YOU, SPONGEBOB.
（咯咯笑）
我喜欢你，海绵宝宝。
WE COULD BE TIGHTER
THAN BARK ON A TREE.
我们可以更紧一些
比树上的树皮。
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
UH, I LIKE YOU
TOO, SANDY.
呃，我喜欢你
还有，桑迪。
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
WHAT IS THAT ON YOUR HEAD?
你头上的是什么？
THAT'S MY AIR HELMET.
这是我的空气头盔。
MAY I TRY IT ON?
我可以试穿吗？
HECK NO,
I NEED IT TO BREATHE.
哎呀不，
我需要它来呼吸。
I GOT TO HAVE MY AIR.
我必须呼吸空气。
ME, TOO!
我也是！
I LOVE AIR.
我喜欢空气。
AIR IS GOOD.
空气很好。
NO KIDDING?
别开玩笑了？
WHY, AIR IS MY MIDDLE NAME.
为什么，空气是我的中间名。
THE MORE AIR, THE BETTER.
空气越多越好。
CAN'T GET ENOUGH AIR.
无法获得足够的空气。
( drawling ):
SHOOT!
（画画）：
射击！
HOW ABOUT COMING OVER TOMORROW
FOR TEA AND COOKIES THEN?
明天过来怎么样
那么茶和饼干呢？
DON'T BE LATE.
不要迟到。
OKAY, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
好的，明天见。
PATRICK!
帕特里克！
PATRICK, PATRICK, PATRICK!
帕特里克，帕特里克，帕特里克！
WHAT'S AIR?
什么是空气？
HUH?
嗯？
I JUST MET THIS GIRL.
我刚刚认识这个女孩。
SHE WEARS A HAT FULL OF... AIR.
她戴着一顶充满……空气的帽子。
DO YOU MEAN SHE "PUTS ON AIRS"?
你的意思是她“装腔作势”吗？
I GUESS SO.
大概吧。
THAT'S JUST FANCY TALK.
这只是空谈。
IF YOU WANT TO BE FANCY
如果你想变得漂亮
HOLD YOUR PINKY UP LIKE THIS.
像这样举起你的小指。
THE HIGHER YOU HOLD IT,
THE FANCIER YOU ARE.
你握得越高，
你就是这样的鸽友。
HOW'S THAT?
怎么样？
HIGHER.
更高。
LIKE THAT?
喜欢这样吗？
NOW, THAT'S FANCY!
现在，太棒了！
THEY SHOULD CALL YOU
SPONGEBOB FANCYPANTS.
他们应该给你打电话
海绵宝宝花式裤。
REMEMBER, WHEN IN DOUBT,
PINKY OUT.
请记住，当有疑问时，
小指出来了。
YOU CAN DO IT,
SPONGEBOB.
你可以做到，
海绵宝宝。
I'LL BE WATCHING.
我会看着的。
THANKS, PAL.
谢谢，朋友。
( rings bell )
（铃声响起）
Hello?
你好？
HIYA, SANDY.
IT'S ME, SPONGEBOB.
你好，桑迪。
是我，海绵宝宝。
Hold on,
I'll let you in.
坚持住，
我会让你进来的。
( buzzing )
（嗡嗡声）
( whistling )
（吹口哨）
( drain gurgling )
（下水道潺潺声）
( stifled whistling )
（压抑的口哨声）
( yelling ):
SANDY!
（大喊）：
桑迪！
OPEN UP!
打开！
SANDY! SANDY!
沙！沙！
SANDY, SOMETHING'S GONE
TERRIBLY WRONG.
桑迪，有东西不见了
非常错误。
THERE'S NO WATER IN...
里面没有水了...
HERE.
这里。
'COURSE THERE'S NO WATER.
当然没有水。
NOTHING BUT AIR.
除了空气什么都没有。
NO WATER?
没有水？
THAT AIN'T A PROBLEM,
IS IT?
这不是问题，
是吗？
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
PROBLEM?
问题？
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
THAT'S HOW I LIKE
MY AIR.
这就是我喜欢的方式
我的空气。
( inhales deeply )
（深吸一口气）
( gagging, coughing )
（作呕、咳嗽）
WITH NO WATER.
没有水。
Sandy:
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
桑迪：
好吧，好吧。
I MADE TEXAS TEA AND COOKIES.
我做了德克萨斯茶和饼干。
WELL, COME ON IN.
好吧，进来吧。
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
( legs squeaking )
（腿吱吱作响）
THAT'S NOT IN.
那不在。
IN!
在！
( squeaking... )
（吱吱声……）
YOU'RE A FUNNY LITTLE DUDE.
你是个有趣的小家伙。
COME ON, I'LL GIVE YOU
THE GRAND TOUR.
来吧，我给你
盛大旅行。
SO THIS IS MY OWN
PRIVATE LITTLE
AIR BUBBLE.
所以这是我自己的
私人小
气泡。
THIS AIR
IS THE DRIEST...
这空气
是最干燥的...
( gasps )
（喘气）
PUREST...
最纯粹...
( gasps )
（喘气）
MOST AIRIEST AIR
IN THE WHOLE SEA.
最通风的空气
在整个大海中。
OH, OVER THERE
IS MY BIRDBATH.
哦，在那儿
是我的水盆。
( chirping cheerily )
（欢快地叽叽喳喳）
AND THAT'S MY
OAK TREE.
这就是我的
橡树。
IT PROVIDES ME
WITH EXTRA AIR.
它为我提供
与额外的空气。
THIS DOME IS MADE OF THE
STRONGEST POLYURETHANE;
这个圆顶是由
最强的聚氨酯；
THAT'S A FANCY NAME
FOR PLASTIC.
这是一个很奇特的名字
对于塑料。
AIN'T THAT JUST
THE BEE'S KNEES?
不是吗？
蜜蜂的膝盖？
TELL YOU WHAT, WEREN'T EASY
GETTING HERE NEITHER.
告诉你，这并不容易
到这里都没有。
FIRST, I HAD
TO HITCH IT UP
TO A BIG, OLD...
首先，我有
连接起来
给一个又大又老的...
( grunting )
（咕哝）
( chirping angrily )
（愤怒地叽叽喳喳）
...THAT'S MY TREADMILL.
...那是我的跑步机。
THAT'S HOW I STAY
IN TIPTOP SHAPE.
这就是我留下来的方式
尖顶形状。
OH, COME ON.
哦，来吧。
LET'S HAVE THAT
TEA NOW.
让我们来吧
现在喝茶。
( karate yells )
（空手道大喊）
( gasps )
（喘气）
( knocking on dome )
（敲击穹顶）
PINKY, PINKY!
小指，小指！
( gasps )
（喘气）
I BROUGHT YOU SOME FLOWERS.
我给你带来了一些花。
FOR ME?
为我？
HOW SWEET!
多么甜蜜啊！
YOU OKAY?
你还好吗？
( raspily ):
YES.
（粗暴地）：
是的。
I'M OKAY.
我没事。
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THE FIRST
SEA CRITTER TO EVER VISIT.
你知道，你是第一个
值得一去的海洋生物。
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY.
我无法想象为什么。
CAN I GET
YOU ANYTHING?
我可以得到吗
你有什么事吗？
WATER WOULD BE NICE.
水就好了。
I'M GOING TO PUT
THESE IN A VASE.
我要放
这些在花瓶里。
TAKE YOUR TIME.
慢慢来。
( gasping )
（喘气）
I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
我必须离开这里。
Sandy:
I LIKE YOU, SPONGEBOB.
桑迪：
我喜欢你，海绵宝宝。
WE COULD BE TIGHTER THAN BARK
ON A TREE.
我们可以比树皮更紧
在树上。
Patrick:
WHEN IN DOUBT, PINKY OUT.
帕特里克：
如有疑问，请伸出小指。
I DON'T NEED WATER.
我不需要水。
WATER IS FOR QUITTERS.
水是给戒烟者的。
I DON'T NEED IT.
我不需要它。
I DON'T NEED IT,
I DON'T NEED IT.
我不需要它，
我不需要它。
WHY, THESE FLOWERS
ARE JUST BEAUTIFUL.
为什么，这些花
很漂亮。
THEY'LL LIVE MUCH, MUCH LONGER
他们会活得更久
IN A VASE FULL
OF ICE-COLD WATER.
装满花瓶
冰水。
SO TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF.
请介绍一下您自己。
IT MUST BE FASCINATING
BEING A SEA CRITTER.
它一定很迷人
作为海洋生物。
SPONGEBOB?
海绵宝宝？
( timer dings )
（定时器的声音）
OH, THERE'S THE COOKIES.
哦，这是饼干。
BE RIGHT BACK.
马上回来。
SpongeBob ( thinking ):
I DON'T NEED IT.
海绵宝宝（思考）：
我不需要它。
I DON'T NEED IT.
I DEFINITELY DON'T NEED IT.
我绝对不需要它。
I DON'T NEED IT.
我不需要它。
( howling ):
I NEED IT!
（嚎叫）：
我需要它！
( wheezing )
（喘息）
NO, SPONGEBOB!
不，海绵宝宝！
NO, NO, NO!
不，不，不！
STOP!
停止！
PINKY, PINKY!
小指，小指！
( yelling ):
I'M A QUITTER!
（大喊）：
我是一个戒烟者！
( SpongeBob wailing )
（海绵宝宝哭泣）
YOU CAN'T LEAVE NOW.
你现在不能离开。
YOU'LL BLOW IT.
你会搞砸的。
AIR IS NOT GOOD, PATRICK.
帕特里克，空气不好。
AIR IS NOT GOOD.
空气不好。
YOU'RE JUST BEING SHY.
你只是害羞了。
DON'T WORRY, BUDDY.
别担心，伙计。
YOU'RE DOING FINE.
你做得很好。
( panting heavily )
（气喘吁吁）
I WON'T LET YOU BLOW... THIS.
我不会让你吹……这个。
( wheezing )
（喘息）
( gagging )
（作呕）
WHAT KIND OF PLACE IS THIS?!
这是什么地方？！
THERE'S NO WATER IN HERE!
这里没有水！
I TRIED
TO TELL YOU.
我尝试过
告诉你。
WE GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE!
我们必须得到
离开这里！
YOU'RE DOING IT WRONG.
你做错了。
WAIT, NO,
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT.
等等，不，
我们必须出去。
( door opens, closes )
（门打开、关闭）
COME AND GET IT.
快过来取。
YOU'RE ALL GOING TO LIKE THIS--
你们都会喜欢这个——
( shrieks )
（尖叫声）
( glasses breaking )
（眼镜碎了）
THERE.
那里。
THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.
应该这样做。
IF YOU ALL NEEDED WATER,
YOU SHOULD HAVE ASKED.
如果你们都需要水，
你应该问一下。
I PROPOSE A TOAST:
我提议干杯：
TO NEW FRIENDS!
致新朋友！
HOLD ON A SECOND.
请稍等。
I HOPE YOU ALL LIKE
YOUR TEA STRONG.
我希望你们都喜欢
你的茶很浓。
DRINK UP!
喝吧！
( both slurping )
（两人都发出咕噜声）
All:
AH!
全部：
啊！
and NICKELODEON]
和尼克频道]
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
[标题为
字幕中心
WGBH教育基金会]
[标题为
字幕中心
WGBH教育基金会]